Goodspeed Musicals Scherer Library of Musical Theatre Priority Archive
Goodspeed Musicals
Goodspeed Musicals Scherer Library of Musical Theatre Priority Archive
1824-2000
Collection compiled by Education Manager and Library Director, Joshua Ritter, and Library Advisory Board Member, Ken Bloom.
27 Boxes
Goodspeed Musicals
Ken Bloom, a distinguished theatre historian, playwright, director, record producer, author, and member of the Goodspeed Library Advisory Board consulted with Education Manager and Library Director, Joshua Ritter, to select items to add to the Priority Archive. These valuable items, more than 500 total, include a full original partitur for "West Side Story", a recording of Steven Sondheim performing "Saturday Night", and signed books and letters from countless Broadway legends.
Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Most Items were donated to the Scherer Library of Musical Theatre by Goodspeed Musicals patrons. Some items were originally created by Goodspeed Musicals.
Biography
The Scherer Library of Musical Theatre at Goodspeed is the only library dedicated solely to musical theatre in the world. The collection boasts more than 100,000 items, providing an invaluable resource to academics and professionals around the world. Dedicated to preserving the rich legacy of the art form, the library carefully maintains a comprehensive collection of scores, sheet music, scripts, original cast recordings, programs, photographs, and theatre memorabilia in a facility located in East Haddam, Connecticut. Currently, these reference tools are utilized by Goodspeed staff and the musical theatre community at large in the re-creation and revitalization of period musicals and in the creation and development of new works. To access the online catalog, please click here. Established in the 1970s to provide historical research for Goodspeed productions, the library has evolved into a valuable resource for theatres across the country, as well as students, scholars and the public. The Scherer Library of Musical Theatre is the only specialized library in the country directly connected to a fully professional producing musical theatre.
To visit the Scherer Library of Musical Theatre website, please click on the following link: http://www.goodspeed.org/education-library/library
Scope and Content of Collection
Thanks to a generous grant from the Harold and Mimi Steinberg Charitable Trust, Goodspeed was able to launch the Catalogue and Digitization Project. This project involved the preservation of the Scherer Library's most fragile, valuable, and important items. The following list is a small sample of some of the items, more than 500 total, that were included in the project:
1. Photo of Joseph Jefferson as Rip Van Winkle 2. Letters by Oscar Hammerstein II 3. Archival script of "Du Barry Was a Lady" 4. "Pousse Cafe" Program 5. Labor Stages "Pins and Needles" program 6. Journal from Max Showalters tour with "This is the Army" 7. Goodspeed Muscials archival recording of "Whoopee"
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by format. These include broadsides, libretti, playbills, letters, photos, art prints, periodicals, scores, books, CDs, and other print formats.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Musical theater; Goodspeed Musicals Scherer Library of Musical Theatre
Related Collections
The Special Archive is another artificial archive which contains items that were deemed significant, but not worthy of inclusion in the Priority Archive.
Separated Material
There are two oversized boxes and two smaller boxes that are not stored with the majority of the collection.
Main Reading Room: Black cabinets 2,3,4,6, two boxes on shelves, and two boxes on top of cabinets in Institutional Archives
- Inventory
  - Le Costume Historique (1), 1877; A. Racinet, Library de Firmin-Didot 1877; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 71; Dimensions: 8 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000814 (Box 1*)
  - Le Costume Historique (2), 1877; A. Racinet, Library de Firmin-Didot 1877; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 74; Dimensions: 8 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000822 (Box 1*)
  - Le Costume Historique (3), 1877; A. Racinet, Library de Firmin-Didot 1877; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 85; Dimensions: 8 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000830 (Box 1*)
  - Le Costume Historique (4), 1877; A. Racinet, Library de Firmin-Didot 1878; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 96; Dimensions: 8 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000848 (Box 1*)
  - Theatre Prints, undated; Modern Stage Design (in ziploc bag); Items: 1; Format: Art Prints; Page count: 239; Dimensions: 5 1/2 X 8; Barcode: 35111000002794 (Box 1*)
  - The Green Room Book, undated; Hardbound published 1907 Who's Who of London Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 598; Dimensions: 7.5 x 5; Barcode: 35111000005987 (Box 1*)
  - Simple Simon Simple, undated; Cast of Characters; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3X11; Barcode: 35111000000186 (Box 2*)
  - The Sweetest Girl In Paris, undated; Walnut St. Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.5 X 13; Barcode: 35111000000442 (Box 2*)
  - Babes in Toyland, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.5 X 13; Barcode: 35111000000525 (Box 2*)
  - Yours Truly, 1928; January 1928,starring Leon Errol; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 10.75 x 4.5; Barcode: 35111000000566 (Box 2*)
  - Broadway Portraits, 1929; Hardbound caricatures by Samuel Marx 1929; Items: 1; Format:; Page count: 64; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000002224 (Box 2*)
  - George Gershwin's Songbook, undated; Song book; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 175; Dimensions: 12.5 x 9.75; Barcode: 35111000002240 (Box 2*)
  - The Rogers Brothers in London, 1904; Chestnut St. Opera House, 1904; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 17.5 x 4; Barcode: 35111000003453 (Box 2*)
  - Red Widow, undated; Forrest Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.5 X 15; Barcode: 35111000003479 (Box 2*)
  - Rogers Brothers in Paris, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 12; Barcode: 35111000003636 (Box 2*)
  - Midnight Sons, undated; Lyric Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75 X 13.5; Barcode: 35111000003685 (Box 2*)
  - Oh, Kay!, undated; Lurie Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 6 X 12; Barcode: 35111000003792 (Box 2*)
  - Curfew, undated; Royal Drury; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 7.75 x 11; Barcode: 35111000003834 (Box 2*)
  - Dream City, undated; The Lyric, 1907; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 13.75 x 4.75; Barcode: 35111000004048 (Box 2*)
  - Grand Mogul, undated; Philadelphia, Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 5 X 13.75; Barcode: 35111000004352 (Box 2*)
  - Girl from Montmatre, undated; Forrest Theatre, Philadelphia, 1912; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 13.5 x 4.25; Barcode: 35111000004451 (Box 2*)
  - Othello, undated; starring Edwin Booth, March 16, 1875; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 9.5 x 12; Barcode: 35111000004543 (Box 2*)
  - Gay Musician, undated; Chestnut St. Opera House, Philadelphia, 1908; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 12 x 4.5; Barcode: 35111000004634 (Box 2*)
  - Golden Butterfly, 1908; Forrest Theatre, Philadelphia, 1908; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 13.75 x 3.75; Barcode: 35111000004659 (Box 2*)
  - White Hen, undated; The Lyric Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75 X 13; Barcode: 35111000004683 (Box 2*)
  - Carousel libretto, 1946; Hardbound first edition 1946, autographed by John Raitt, Jean Darling, Bambi Linn; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 187; Dimensions: 7.5 x 5; Barcode: 35111000005821 (Box 2*)
  - Belle of Mayfair, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 5 X 12; Barcode: 35111000000491 (Box 2*)
  - Hans the Flute Player, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 11"; Barcode: 35111000004410 (Box 2*)
  - Humpty Dumpty, undated; Philadelphia, Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4 X 13.5; Barcode: 35111000004436 (Box 2*)
  - Pioneer Days, undated; New York Hippodrome; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 7.5 X 12; Barcode: 35111000004329 (Box 2*)
  - Oh. Kay!, undated; 1989 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 78; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000079 (Box 3)
  - Chocolate Soldier, undated; Lyric Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 11.5; Barcode: 35111000000202 (Box 3)
  - Chinese Honeymoon, undated; Program; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 5 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000000210 (Box 3*)
  - Charlatan, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.5 X 8; Barcode: 35111000000228 (Box 3*)
  - Castles in the Air, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 X 6.75; Barcode: 35111000000236 (Box 3*)
  - Burgomaster, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.25 X 8.75; Barcode: 35111000000277 (Box 3*)
  - Burgomaster, undated; Broad St. Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.25 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000000285 (Box 3*)
  - Broadway Brevities 1920, undated; Pre-Broadway; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 7.75 X 10; Barcode: 35111000000376 (Box 3*)
  - Smugglers of Badayez, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.25 X 7.5; Barcode: 35111000000384 (Box 3*)
  - Panjandrum, undated; Program; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 5.5; Barcode: 35111000000392 (Box 3*)
  - Rose of the Alhambra, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 X 11; Barcode: 35111000000400 (Box 3*)
  - Broadway to Tokyo, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.5 X 7; Barcode: 35111000000459 (Box 3*)
  - Boys and Betty, undated; Carrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.75 X 11; Barcode: 35111000000467 (Box 3*)
  - Blossom Time, undated; Lyric Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3 X 8; Barcode: 35111000000475 (Box 3*)
  - Beautiful Unknown, undated; Adelphi Theatre, Titled My Lady's Glove on Broadway; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000509 (Box 3*)
  - The Milk Train Doesn't Stop Here Anymore, undated; Ford's Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 11 x 7.5; Barcode: 35111000003149 (Box 3*)
  - The Merry Widow and the Devil, 1907; One of the greatest hits in Broadway history. November 1907; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 8.5 x 6; Barcode: 35111000003164 (Box 3*)
  - Mary, 1921; Atkins' Theatre, 1921; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 9 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000003206 (Box 3*)
  - The Pink Lady, undated; Forrest Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 12 x 4; Barcode: 35111000003214 (Box 3*)
  - The Passing Show of 1923, 1924; Sam S. shubert Theatre, 1924, The New York Winter Garden's Annual Revue; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 8 x 6; Barcode: 35111000003230 (Box 3*)
  - The Student Prince, undated; Ford's Theater; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6.25 x 14; Barcode: 35111000003255 (Box 3*)
  - We will let you name it, undated; Music Box TheatreBox 3*; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6 x 9; Barcode: 35111000003263 (Box 3*)
  - Happyland, undated; Program, with DeWolf hopper and Marguerite Clark, Comic opera; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6 X 9; Barcode: 35111000003289 (Box 3*)
  - King Dodo, undated; Nixon & Zimmerman's New Chestnut St. Theatre, 1902; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 8.5; Barcode: 35111000003297 (Box 3*)
  - Sho-Gun, undated; Chestnut St. Theatre, Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 9; Barcode: 35111000003305 (Box 3*)
  - A Princess of Kensington, undated; Chestnut Street Theatre, 1903; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 13.75 x 4; Barcode: 35111000003313 (Box 3*)
  - Afgar, undated; Globe Theater; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 5 x 7; Barcode: 35111000003321 (Box 3*)
  - Cymbeline, undated; Walnut Street Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000003339 (Box 3*)
  - The Prince of Pilsen, undated; Chestnut Street Theatre, September 1903; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10 x 4; Barcode: 35111000003354 (Box 3*)
  - Ziegfeld Follies, undated; New Amsterdam Theatre, 1919.; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 5 X 10"; Barcode: 35111000003438 (Box 3*)
  - The Tourists, undated; The Lyric Theatre, 1906; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 3.5 X 6.75; Barcode: 35111000003552 (Box 3*)
  - The Fascinating Widow, undated; Forrest Theatre, Nixon & Zimmerman Theatre Co.; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10 x 4.25; Barcode: 35111000003560 (Box 3*)
  - School Girl, undated; Chestnut St. Opera House, Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 5.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000003578 (Box 3*)
  - Student King, 1906; Chestnut Street Theatre, 1906; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.5 X 8.75; Barcode: 35111000003586 (Box 3*)
  - Some Time, undated; Casino Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 5 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000003594 (Box 3*)
  - Damn Yankees, undated; Shubert Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 6 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000003628 (Box 3*)
  - Miss Simplicity, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.5 X 7.75; Barcode: 35111000003644 (Box 3*)
  - Roberta, undated; Parsons Theatre, Hartford; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 5 X 8; Barcode: 35111000003677 (Box 3*)
  - Keep Kool, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 4.25 X 6; Barcode: 35111000003701 (Box 3*)
  - The Tourists in the Pullman Palace Car, undated; Park Theatre, 1880; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10 x 5; Barcode: 35111000003719 (Box 3*)
  - Fanny, undated; Shubert Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 6 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000003727 (Box 3*)
  - Man Who Owns Broadway, undated; Forrest Theatre, Philadelphia, 1910; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 11 x 8.5; Barcode: 35111000003735 (Box 3*)
  - Miss Dolly Dollars, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4 X 9; Barcode: 35111000003743 (Box 3*)
  - King Dodo, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.75 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000003750 (Box 3*)
  - San Toy, undated; Chestnut Street Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.5 X 5.25; Barcode: 35111000003768 (Box 3*)
  - Happyland, undated; The Lyric Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4 X 7.25; Barcode: 35111000003776 (Box 3*)
  - Knickerbockers, undated; Broad St. Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.5 X 9; Barcode: 35111000003784 (Box 3*)
  - Greenwich Village Follies, undated; 1922-4th Edition; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6 X 8; Barcode: 35111000003800 (Box 3*)
  - Higgledy-Piggledy, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 5 X 8.25; Barcode: 35111000003818 (Box 3*)
  - The Riviera Girl, 1917; Sept. 1917 by Guy Bolton and PG Wodehouse; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4 x 9.75; Barcode: 35111000003859 (Box 3*)
  - Stars in Your Eyes, undated; Majestic Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000003875 (Box 3*)
  - Serenade, undated; Chestnut St. Opera House, Philadelphia, 1897; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 8.25 x 3.5; Barcode: 35111000003925 (Box 3*)
  - Cross My Heart, undated; Knickerbocker Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 7.25 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000003933 (Box 3*)
  - Lady Teazle, undated; Featuring Lillian Russell, one of the first great stars of Broadway.; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10.75 x 4; Barcode: 35111000003958 (Box 3*)
  - Miss Moffat, undated; Bette Davis' only book musical; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000003966 (Box 3*)
  - When Sweet Sixteen, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 11; Barcode: 35111000003982 (Box 3*)
  - White Chrysanthemum, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75 X 7; Barcode: 35111000003990 (Box 3*)
  - Debutante, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4 X 9; Barcode: 35111000004006 (Box 3*)
  - Yankee Consul, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75 X 11; Barcode: 35111000004014 (Box 3*)
  - Sons O' Fun, undated; Forrest Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 6 X 9; Barcode: 35111000004022 (Box 3*)
  - Viceroy, undated; Broad Street Theatre, Philadelphia, 1900; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6.5 x 3.5; Barcode: 35111000004030 (Box 3*)
  - Vanderbilt Cup, undated; The Garrick Theatre, Philadelphia, 1906; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 7 x 9.5; Barcode: 35111000004055 (Box 3*)
  - Circus Girl, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.5 X 7; Barcode: 35111000004063 (Box 3*)
  - School Girl, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000004212 (Box 3*)
  - The Merry Widow, undated; New Amsterdam Theatre, 1907; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 9 x 5.75; Barcode: 35111000004220 (Box 3*)
  - Nancy Brown, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75 X 11; Barcode: 35111000004238 (Box 3*)
  - Molly Darling, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 3; Dimensions: 4.5 X 6; Barcode: 35111000004246 (Box 3*)
  - New Yorkers (1902), undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 11; Barcode: 35111000004253 (Box 3*)
  - Tattooed Man, undated; Broad St. Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 5.5 X 7; Barcode: 35111000004261 (Box 3*)
  - Pearl and the Pumpkin, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 3.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000004279 (Box 3*)
  - Mlle. Modiste, undated; Colonial Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 5 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000004287 (Box 3*)
  - Robin Hood, undated; Garden Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 7 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000004295 (Box 3*)
  - Quaker Girl, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000004303 (Box 3*)
  - Love Cure, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.75 X 11; Barcode: 35111000004311 (Box 3*)
  - Rose Maid, undated; Philadelphia, Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.5 X 14; Barcode: 35111000004360 (Box 3*)
  - Hoyden, undated; Knick-Bocker Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6 X 9; Barcode: 35111000004378 (Box 3 *)
  - Serenade, undated; Broad St. Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.5 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004386 (Box 3*)
  - Maid Marian, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 8.75; Barcode: 35111000004394 (Box 3*)
  - Isle of Spice, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 5 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000004402 (Box 3*)
  - European and American Vaudeville, undated; Hammerstein, Theatre of Varieties; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 9.5 x 6.25; Barcode: 35111000004428 (Box 3*)
  - Rogers Brothers in Ireland, undated; Chestnut Street Opera House; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 3.75 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000004444 (Box 3*)
  - Gay White Way, undated; Casino Theatre, Broadway, 1907; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 7.5 x 5.75; Barcode: 35111000004469 (Box 3*)
  - Fluffy Ruffles, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10.75 x 4; Barcode: 35111000004485 (Box 3*)
  - Foxy Quiller, 1901; The Klaw and Erlanger Opera Company, 1901; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 7.25 x 3.25; Barcode: 35111000004493 (Box 3*)
  - Pal Joey, undated; Signed by cast. One of the earliest Broadway revivals, It kicked off the spate of revivals to follow.; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 8.5 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000004527 (Box 3*)
  - Pacific Overtures, undated; Winter Garden Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside 2 copies; Page count: 2 & 2; Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000004550 (Box 3*)
  - Dr. Syntax, undated; Chestnut St. Opera House, Philadelphia, 1894; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6.75 x 3.75; Barcode: 35111000004576 (Box 3*)
  - 50 Miles from Boston, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6.75 x 4.25; Barcode: 35111000004584 (Box 3*)
  - Enchantress, 1911; Chestnut St. Opera House, Philadelphia, 1911; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10.25 x 4.5; Barcode: 35111000004592 (Box 3*)
  - Frederika, undated; Imperial Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000004600 (Box 3*)
  - Fascinating Flora, 1907; Lyric Theatre, 1907; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 9 x 4.5; Barcode: 35111000004626 (Box 3*)
  - Erminie, undated; Revival, Forrest Theatre, Philadelphia, 1921; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 8.75 x 3; Barcode: 35111000004642 (Box 3*)
  - Wild Rose, undated; Philadelphia; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.75 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000004667 (Box 3*)
  - Babette, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75 X 10.75; Barcode: 35111000000517 (Box 3*)
  - Wonderland, undated; Chestnut Street theatre; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 3.25 X 10; Barcode: 35111000004071 (Box 3*)
  - Secret Agent, 1855; Theatre Royal Hay-Market July 26, 1855; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 9 x 20; Barcode: 35111000005177 (Box 4*)
  - School for Scheming, undated; Theatre Royal Hay-market April 20, 1847; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 20 x 9.5; Barcode: 35111000005284 (Box 4*)
  - Drury Lane Renovation, undated; Announcement of interior alterations for the Theatre Royal Drury Lane; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 8.75 x 13; Barcode: 35111000005318 (Box 4*)